{
    "subject": "Srinagarindra",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Mahidol_Adulyadej",
    "human_readable": "Srinagarindra is married to Mahidol Adulyadej.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9678869247436523,
            "question": "What can you say about the marriage of Srinagarindra and Mahidol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9310362935066223,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Srinagarindra and Mahidol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9243302941322327,
            "question": "Who is Srinagarindra married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9112338423728943,
            "question": "To whom did Srinagarindra get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9099761843681335,
            "question": "Is Mahidol Adulyadej married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7764770984649658,
            "question": "What is the name of Mahidol Adulyadej's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681725025177002,
            "question": "Is Srinagarindra in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7668885588645935,
            "question": "What is the name of Mahidol Adulyadej's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7201961278915405,
            "question": "Who is Srinagarindra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6981944441795349,
            "question": "Who is Mahidol Adulyadej?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Srinagarindra is married to Mahidol Adulyadej.",
            "html": "yago_30173_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Srinagarindra?",
            "html": "yago_30173_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Mahidol Adulyadej's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30173_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Srinagarindra in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30173_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30173_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Srinagarindra is married to Mahidol Adulyadej\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention Srinagarindra as being married to Prince Mahidol Adulyadej, and also mention him as her husband."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Srinagarindra is married to Mahidol Adulyadej.\" Multiple sources confirm their marriage, with details such as the year (1920) and location (Bangkok)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}